ipaddressguide.com 2010-10-07

# Privacy Policy

* * *

****

IPAddressGuide.com Privacy Statement

Updated: **May 20, 2005**

Please read this agreement carefully and completely before using this site. 

_IPAddressGuide.com_ (the “ _IAG_ ”) is committed to protecting your privacy. This privacy statement explains data collection and use practices of the _IPAddressGuide.com_ site (the “Site”). By accessing the Site, you are consenting to the information collection and use practices described in this privacy statement.

**Use of Personal Information**   
When you visit and navigate the Site and when you communicate with us via the Site, we will not collect personal information about you unless you provide us that information voluntarily. Any non-public personal information that you may provide via our sites will be used solely for the purpose stated on the page where it is collected. _IPAddressGuide.com_ will not sell, license, transmit or disclose this information outside of _IAG_ and its affiliated companies unless   
(a) expressly authorized by you, or   
(b) necessary to enable contractors or agents to perform certain functions as requested by you, or   
(c) required or permitted by law. 

**Use of Visitor IP Address**   
An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you begin service with an Internet Service Provider. We collect IP addresses for the purposes of system administration and to audit the use of our site. Each time you log onto our site and each time you request one of our pages, our server logs your IP address. Although we log your session with us, we will not normally link your IP address to anything that can enable us to identify you. However, we can and will use IP addresses to identify a user when we feel it is necessary to enforce compliance with our rules or terms of service or to protect our service, site, users or others. 

**Use of Cookies and Web Beacons**   
_IPAddressGuide.com_ may contains cookies on this Site to ensure the integrity of the registration process and to personalize the Site. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a Web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. 

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. For example, if you personalize a web page, or navigate within a site, a cookie helps the site to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of delivering relevant content, eases site navigation, and so on. When you return to the Web site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the site's features that you customized. 

Web beacons, also known as clear gif technology, or action tags, may be used to assist in delivering the cookie on our site. This technology is a tool we use to compile aggregated statistics about Microsoft.com Web site usage, such as how many visitors clicked on key elements (such as links or graphics) on a Microsoft.com Web page, blog or a newsletter. We may share aggregated site statistics with partner companies. 

Some of these Web beacons may be placed by third party service providers to help determine the effectiveness of our advertising campaigns or email communications. These Web beacons may be used by these service providers to place a persistent cookie on your computer. Doing this allows the service provider to recognize your computer each time you visit certain pages or emails and compile anonymous information in relation to those page views. _IPAddressGuide.com_ prohibits Web beacons from being used to collect or access your personal information. 

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of this or other Web sites you visit. 

**Changes to this Statement**   
We may occasionally update this privacy statement. When we do, we will also revise the "last updated" date at the top of the privacy statement. For material changes to this privacy statement, we will notify you either by placing a prominent notice on the home page of our Web site or by directly sending you a notification. We encourage you to periodically review this privacy statement to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. Your continued use of the service constitutes your agreement to this privacy statement and any updates. 

**Contact Information**   
_IPAddressGuide.com_ welcomes your comments regarding this privacy statement. If you believe that _IPAddressGuide.com_ has not adhered to this privacy statement, please contact us electronically at the email address provided below, and we will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem. 

* * *

**|Ping |  Traceroute | IP2Location™ | NSLookup |  Deobsfucator | CIDR |  IP Decimal | HTML Validator | [Free Bandwidth Speed Test](http://speedtest.ipaddressguide.com/) | Whois  
**|Home | [Email](mailto:support@ipaddressguide.com) |**  
Copyright © 2005 - 2010 IPAddressGuide.com. All rights reserved.  Privacy Statement. Terms of Service.IP2Location™ is a registered trademark of [ http://www.ip2location.com](http://www.ip2location.com/) ******
